co.vu 2016-01-04

# codotvu.com

### Privacy Statement

* * *

Your privacy is critically important to us. At co.vu we have a few fundamental principles:

  * **We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.**
  * **We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.**
  * **We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.**

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, co.vu collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Purpose of collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how co.vu's visitors use its website. From time to time, co.vu may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

co.vu also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to co.vu's websites choose to interact with co.vu in ways that require co.vu to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that co.vu gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with co.vu are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, co.vu collects such information only in so far as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with co.vu. Co.vu does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Aggregated Statistics

co.vu may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, co.vu may monitor the most popular links or screen the links help identify spam. co.vu may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, co.vu does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

co.vu will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. co.vu discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when co.vu believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of co.vu, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of an co.vu website and have supplied your email address, co.vu may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with co.vu and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. co.vu takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. co.vu uses cookies to help co.vu identify and track visitors, their usage of co.vu website, and their website access preferences. co.vu visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using co.vu's websites, with the drawback that certain features of co.vu's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Business Transfers

If co.vu, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that co.vu goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of co.vu may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, co.vu may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in co.vu's sole discretion. co.vu encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

###  __

Login to your account to register this domain

### Sign In

Your username or password was incorrect.

Use Your Email To Login

Your username or password was incorrect.

Not a registered user. [Sign Up](http://codotvu.com/#)

###  __

Create an account to register this domain

### Create An Account

Use Your Email To Login

Not a registered user. [Login](http://codotvu.com/#)

### Forgot your password?

Please enter your email address below and we will send you an email with a link to reset your password.
